The Ridiculous 6 is a western, comedy, action film directed by Frank Coraci.
When his long-lost outlaw father returns, Tommy "White Knife" Stockburn goes on an
adventure-filled journey across the Old West with his five brothers.
Tommy, played by Adam Sandler.
Chico, played by Terry Crews.
Herm, played by Jorge Garcia.
Lil Pete, played by Taylor Lautner.
Ramon, played by Rob Schneider.
Danny, played by Luke Wilson.
The Ridiculous 6 is a 2015 American Western action comedy film directed by Frank Coraci and written by Tim Herlihy and Adam
Sandler, and starring Sandler, Terry Crews, Jorge Garcia, Taylor Lautner, Rob Schneider, and Luke Wilson.
As Happy Madison Productions' first Western film, as well as their first under Netflix, the plot follows six men who
discover that they share the same bank-robbing father (Nick Nolte) and thereafter set out to reunite with him.
Released worldwide on Netflix on December 11, 2015, the film was panned by critics and is
one of the few films to receive an approval rating of 0% on Rotten Tomatoes.
The tone is lighthearted.